♪ IT KILLS ME NOT TO KNOW THIS ♪
♪ BUT I'VE ALL BUT
JUST FORGOTTEN ♪
♪ WHAT THE COLOR
OF HER EYES WERE ♪
♪ AND HER SCARS OR
HOW SHE GOT THEM ♪
♪ AS THE TELLING SIGNS
OF AGE RAIN DOWN ♪
♪ A SINGLE TEAR IS DROPPING ♪
♪ THROUGH THE VALLEYS
OF AN AGING FACE ♪
♪ THAT THIS WORLD
HAS FORGOTTEN ♪
(HEAVY ROCK MUSIC)
♪ THERE IS NO RECONCILIATION ♪
♪ THAT WILL PUT ME IN MY PLACE ♪
♪ AND THERE IS NO TIME
LIKE THE PRESENT ♪
♪ TO DRINK THESE
DRAINING SECONDS ♪
♪ BUT SELDOM DO THESE
WORDS RING TRUE ♪
♪ WHEN I'M CONSTANTLY
FAILING YOU ♪
♪ WALLS THAT WE JUST
CAN'T BREAK THROUGH ♪
♪ UNTIL WE DISAPPEAR ♪
♪ SO TELL ME NOW ♪
♪ IF THIS AIN'T LOVE
THEN HOW DO WE GET OUT ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN SHE SAID ♪
♪ I DON'T HATE YOU BOY ♪
♪ I JUST WANNA SAVE YOU ♪
♪ WHILE THERE'S STILL
SOMETHING LEFT TO SAVE ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN I TOLD
HER, I LOVE YOU GIRL ♪
♪ BUT I'M NOT THE ANSWER ♪
♪ FOR THE QUESTIONS
THAT YOU STILL HAVE ♪
♪ OH, OH ♪
♪ AND THE DAY PRESSED ON
LIKE CRUSHING WEIGHTS ♪
♪ FOR NO MAN DOES IT EVER WAIT ♪
♪ LIKE MEMORIES OF DYING DAYS ♪
♪ THAT DEAFEN US
LIKE HURRICANES ♪
♪ BATHED IN FLAMES
WE HELD THE BRAND ♪
♪ UNCURLED THE
FINGERS IN YOUR HAND ♪
♪ PRESSED INTO THE
FLESH LIKE SAND ♪
♪ NOW DO YOU UNDERSTAND ♪
♪ SO TELL ME NOW ♪
♪ IF THIS AIN'T LOVE
THEN HOW DO WE GET OUT ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN SHE SAID ♪
♪ I DON'T HATE YOU BOY ♪
♪ I JUST WANNA SAVE YOU ♪
♪ WHILE THERE'S STILL
SOMETHING LEFT TO SAVE ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN I TOLD
HER, I LOVE YOU GIRL ♪
♪ BUT I'M NOT THE ANSWER ♪
♪ FOR THE QUESTIONS
THAT YOU STILL HAVE ♪
♪ OH, OH ♪
♪ 1,000 MILES AWAY ♪
♪ THERE'S NOTHING LEFT TO SAY ♪
♪ BUT SO MUCH LEFT
THAT I DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ WE NEVER HAD A CHOICE ♪
♪ THIS WORLD IS TOO MUCH NOISE ♪
♪ IT TAKES ME UNDER ♪
♪ IT TAKES ME UNDER ONCE AGAIN ♪
(SLOW ROCK MUSIC)
♪ I DON'T HATE YOU ♪
♪ I DON'T HATE YOU, NO ♪
♪ SO TELL ME NOW ♪
♪ IF THIS AIN'T LOVE
THEN HOW DO WE GET OUT ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN SHE SAID ♪
♪ I DON'T HATE YOU BOY ♪
♪ I JUST WANNA SAVE YOU ♪
♪ WHILE THERE'S STILL
SOMETHING LEFT TO SAVE ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN I TOLD
HER, I LOVE YOU GIRL ♪
♪ BUT I'M NOT THE ANSWER ♪
♪ FOR THE QUESTIONS
THAT YOU STILL HAVE ♪
♪ OH, OH ♪
♪ I DON'T HATE YOU ♪
♪ I DON'T HATE YOU, NO ♪
♪ OH, OH ♪